https://californialongtermcare.com/privacy/

Your Personal Information is Safe with Us
California Long Term Care Insurance Services, Inc. and North Star Network Insurance Agency, Inc. are committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. Your personal information is safe with us.
Your Personal Information is Used Only to Serve You
Any personal (i.e. identifying) information that you provide will be used to help transact your business, respond to your questions, and optimize your use of our website and services.
We will not sell, rent, or give any personal information to any unaffiliated party for purposes unrelated to servicing your requests (unless required to do so by law or other regulatory authority.)
Non-Personal Information Anonymously Collected for Marketing Purpose
Like many companies, to learn how we can reach more people who may benefit from our long term care insurance services, we use Google Analytics to collect non-personal information such as which webpage visitors visited and which advertisements they clicked on.
All of this information is collected anonymously. Your personal information is never attached to information collected for marketing purposes.
Your personal information is never associated with marketing information and you may opt out of having marketing information collected through Google. You can opt out here http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en
Google also collects information such as mouse clicks, mouse movements and scrolling activity, browser type, operating system, access times, and Internet Protocol (IP) address.
However, the actual IP address is never disclosed by Google; it’s used only to identify the country, state, and city of our website users. This helps us know how our website is working and where to put our marketing dollars to reach people who need our services.
Here is a link to Google’s Privacy Policy: http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html
Updates to Our Privacy Policy
If it is necessary to modify our privacy policy, you will find those changes right here; if it is a significant change, we will post notice of the update on our home page.
How to Contact Us if You have Privacy Policy Questions or Concerns
Should you have any questions or concerns about the use of information collected on our site, please contact us via email at privacy@cltcinsurance.com. We welcome your inquiry.
“The Future is Yours to Plan”Start Here
Enter your information below to download your Guide and to request your Free Consultation and Quotes.
First Name:*
Please enter your first name.
Last Name:*
Please enter your Last name.
Email: *
Please enter your Email Address.
Phone : *
Please enter your Phone.
Zip
: *
Not a real zip code.
Captcha:*
Your information is safe with us and will not be shared : Privacy
Long term Care Facts & Testimonials
8 hours per day of care at home can now cost over $60,000 per year, and an average period of care approaches three years.
2013-05-24T04:37:02+00:00
8 hours per day of care at home can now cost over $60,000 per year, and an average period of care approaches three years.
https://californialongtermcare.com/testimonials/8-hour-par-day/
Women are 50% more likely than men to need long-term care. This is due to  women's additional life expectancy and their greater historical use of long-term care.
2013-05-24T04:37:48+00:00
Women are 50% more likely than men to need long-term care. This is due to women's additional life expectancy and their greater historical use of long-term care.
https://californialongtermcare.com/testimonials/women/
Women represent 70-80% of long-term care insurance claims. Long-term care insurance companies are finally realizing they need to alter their pricing model to account for the added cost of insuring women.
2013-05-24T05:00:25+00:00
Women represent 70-80% of long-term care insurance claims. Long-term care insurance companies are finally realizing they need to alter their pricing model to account for the added cost of insuring women.
https://californialongtermcare.com/testimonials/265/
The government will not provide long term care for people with assets. Medicare covers little and Medicaid covers nothing if you have assets.
This makes you responsible for your own care.
2013-05-24T05:00:41+00:00
The government will not provide long term care for people with assets. Medicare covers little and Medicaid covers nothing if you have assets. This makes you responsible for your own care.
https://californialongtermcare.com/testimonials/266/
When you need Long Term Care coverage, you won't be able to get it.
Without coverage, you are “self-insured” and exposed to the greatest threat to your retirement – the full cost of long-term care.
2013-05-24T05:00:55+00:00
When you need Long Term Care coverage, you won't be able to get it. Without coverage, you are “self-insured” and exposed to the greatest threat to your retirement – the full cost of long-term care.
https://californialongtermcare.com/testimonials/267/
